<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blog &#8211; The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/category/blog-post/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 12:57:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>What You Should Consider When Choosing a Lash Style</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/10/07/what-you-should-consider-when-choosing-a-lash-style/</link>
					<comments>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/10/07/what-you-should-consider-when-choosing-a-lash-style/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ebenezer Eyelash]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 12:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7872</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eyelash extensions may be the most exciting beauty enhancement to hit the marketplace in generations, but there’s no doubt that they’re not for the faint of heart. In fact, any woman considering extensions should probably have a firm understanding of exactly what she’s hoping to achieve. After all, lash extensions can come in a variety...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/10/07/what-you-should-consider-when-choosing-a-lash-style/">What You Should Consider When Choosing a Lash Style</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2017/08/30/eyelash-extensions-and-your-new-beauty-routine/">Eyelash extensions</a> may be the most exciting beauty enhancement to hit the marketplace in generations, but there’s no doubt that they’re not for the faint of heart. In fact, any woman considering extensions should probably have a firm understanding of exactly what she’s hoping to achieve. After all, lash extensions can come in a variety of forms, and accomplish a number of different beauty goals – from simplifying your beauty regimen to creating a dramatic lash look that’s impossible to hide. Before choosing your lash style, here are just a few of the things you should consider.</p>
<h2>How Dramatic is Too Dramatic?</h2>
<p>One of the best things about <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/eyelash-extension-services/">eyelash extensions</a> is that they can help you create so many different lash styles. Of course, some women go all-out with their lashes, and opt for the most dramatic look possible. They want long, thick, movie star lashes with that perfect curl their natural lashes could never achieve. Other women want a more understated look – perfect lashes that provide that everyday beauty aesthetic and a change that only their closest friends and family are likely to notice.</p>
<p>Before you choose, it’s important to consider just how dramatic you want your lash change to be. Are you looking for a truly glamorous look fit for a special event like a wedding? Or are you just looking for a way to achieve perfect lashes without going through the hassle of applying mascara and using a lash curler? To get your lashes just right, you’ll need to make that decision and discuss it with your lash artist before your application.</p>
<h2>What Style Best Fits Your Eyes?</h2>
<p>You’ll also need to consider your eyes’ shape, and the shape of your brow, if you want to pick the perfect lash style for your face. For example, if you have a thick brow bone and deep-set eyes, you can generally get away with longer, more voluminous lashes than normal. Round eyes tend to do extremely well with a cat’s eye style that has added volume at the outside edges of the eye. If your eyes are already your most prominent feature, you may want to try a style using varying lash lengths to provide a natural – but still stunning – lash look.</p>
<h2>How Much Maintenance Can You Tolerate?</h2>
<p>Of course, maintenance is also a factor. Some of the most dramatic looks may require more ongoing maintenance than you’re willing to endure, so you should think about that as well. How often do you want to commit to refills?</p>
<p>As you can see, there are a lot of things to consider when you’re choosing your own lash style. That’s why it’s so important to consult with the lash artists at Ebenezer Eyelash to ensure that your choice is the best one for your unique lifestyle and beauty needs. With proper consultation and the <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/">best eyelash extension services in New York City</a>, you can rest assured that your style will always keep you looking and feeling your best. Call us today to schedule your next consultation and lash extension application.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/10/07/what-you-should-consider-when-choosing-a-lash-style/">What You Should Consider When Choosing a Lash Style</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/10/07/what-you-should-consider-when-choosing-a-lash-style/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why You Should Never Forget to Brush Your Lashes</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/30/why-you-should-never-forget-to-brush-your-lashes/</link>
					<comments>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/30/why-you-should-never-forget-to-brush-your-lashes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ebenezer Eyelash]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 07:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eyelash brushing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7852</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>While lash extensions continue to be one of the hottest beauty crazes on the planet today, far too many women never bother to take the time to learn how to properly care for them. Many extension-wearers fail to follow through on their aftercare responsibilities, and that often leads to problems down the road. Some are...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/30/why-you-should-never-forget-to-brush-your-lashes/">Why You Should Never Forget to Brush Your Lashes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>While lash extensions continue to be one of the hottest beauty crazes on the planet today, far too many women never bother to take the time to learn how to properly care for them. Many extension-wearers fail to follow through on their aftercare responsibilities, and that often leads to problems down the road. Some are left to lament as the extensions fall our prematurely. Others end up with tangled or broken extensions. In almost every instance, problems could have been easily avoided had those women committed to proper aftercare. And one of the most important elements of that aftercare is daily lash brushing.</p>
<p>Of course, there are good reasons why you should never forget to brush your lashes and extensions. For that matter, you should be brushing your lashes daily even if you’re not wearing extensions – and for many of the same reasons that you brush the hair on your head. The fact is that hair – including the follicles that support your extensions – requires regular maintenance to remain at its cleanest and healthiest best. Need more reasons to always remember your daily lash brushing? Try these:</p>
<ul>
<li>When you brush your extensions, you can help to remove any dust, pollen, oils, or eye makeup that may accumulate on the lashes throughout the day. Brushing dislodges those particles more effectively than your daily wash and rinse, preventing buildup over time.</li>
<li>Daily brushing can remove bacteria that could cause irritation of the eyes or even infection. To avoid those problems, make sure to use a mild cleaner, clear water rinse, and a clean lash brush to gently comb through your lashes and extensions.</li>
<li>Brushing is also an important part of your overall lash maintenance routine. When you brush each day, you can help to keep your lashes and extensions from becoming tangled, bent, or unkempt. That will ensure that you maintain their aesthetic appeal, while preventing them from suffering unnecessary damage or wear and tear.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Brushing Properly</h2>
<p>Naturally, you need to know how to brush properly. These tips can help:</p>
<ul>
<li>Always use a clean lash brush or mascara wand to avoid transferring bacteria to the eyes.</li>
<li>Brush from the middle of the extension to the end of the lash. Never start at the base, since that could result in the brush pulling the extension out.</li>
<li>For optimal results, brush the bottom of your extensions and the top of each lash. That’s the best way to ensure that you remove every offending particle of dust, oil, or debris.</li>
<li>Do this at least once a day. While it’s good to have an established routine and a set time for brushing, don’t be afraid to brush whenever you notice lashes going in the wrong direction or looking otherwise disheveled.</li>
</ul>
<p>At Ebenezer Eyelash, we know that your lash extensions are an important beauty investment, and we want to help you keep them looking their best for as long as possible. After all, when you get the <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/">best eyelash extensions in New York City</a>, you expect them to last! Call us today to learn more, or to schedule your next lash extension appointment.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/30/why-you-should-never-forget-to-brush-your-lashes/">Why You Should Never Forget to Brush Your Lashes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/30/why-you-should-never-forget-to-brush-your-lashes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Best Beauty Tip You’ll Ever Receive: Get Lash Extensions!</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/22/the-best-beauty-tip-youll-ever-receive-get-lash-extensions/</link>
					<comments>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/22/the-best-beauty-tip-youll-ever-receive-get-lash-extensions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ebenezer Eyelash]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 08:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eyelash Extensions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7858</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Most of us are always eager to hear the latest beauty tips – and who can blame us? After all, modern society is often consumed with aesthetic concerns, and personal appearance remains a top priority for many Americans. Still, the majority of beauty tips tend to be either overly complicated or ridiculously simplistic. Worse, far...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/22/the-best-beauty-tip-youll-ever-receive-get-lash-extensions/">The Best Beauty Tip You’ll Ever Receive: Get Lash Extensions!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Most of us are always eager to hear the latest beauty tips – and who can blame us? After all, modern society is often consumed with aesthetic concerns, and personal appearance remains a top priority for many Americans. Still, the majority of beauty tips tend to be either overly complicated or ridiculously simplistic. Worse, far too many simply don’t work for large numbers of women. Fortunately, there are some <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2017/03/28/tips-for-living-with-lash-extensions/">beauty tips</a> that are virtually guaranteed to work – and the tip you’re about to receive is one of them. In fact, this might just be the <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2018/02/21/five-things-your-lash-technician-wants-you-to-know/">best beauty tip</a> you’ll ever receive. Simply put, get lash extensions!</p>
<h2>A Superior Beauty Solution</h2>
<p>Lash extensions are a powerful option to give you those perfect lashes all women crave. They’ve been a popular solution for many of the world’s rich and famous for many years but have gained renown across all levels of society in recent decades. That’s right; though lash extensions were once the province of Hollywood stars and other wealthy women, they’re now available for women of all walks of life.</p>
<p>That newfound popularity and prevalence is perhaps one of the greatest developments in health and beauty in many, many years. Prior to the rise of extensions, women with inferior lashes were often consigned to a lifetime of excessive mascara, false eyelashes, or social discomfort. Now, almost any woman who wants perfect lashes can have them – and all the benefits they provide.</p>
<h3>Extensions Can Change Your Life</h3>
<p>Lash Extensions can have a powerful impact on every area of your life. If you’ve long suffered from short, listless lashes that do nothing to frame your eyes and highlight your dazzling beauty, then eyelash extensions could be the perfect answer. With extensions, you get:</p>
<ul>
<li>Longer lashes that provide that soft, fluttery lash look long associated with ‘perfect lashes’</li>
<li>Thicker lashes and the type of volume that mascara can only pretend to imitate</li>
<li>Perfectly-curled lashes that help to open up your eyes, creating the illusion of bigger, brighter eyes</li>
<li>A more youthful appearance, as your new lashes help to focus attention on one of your most youthful features: the eyes</li>
</ul>
<p>Of course, those are just the physical effects. In addition, you’ll finally be able to cut back on your use of mascara and other makeup products, since your extensions will do that mascara’s job for it. Naturally, that reduced reliance on makeup will provide another important benefit too: more free time to do the things you love.</p>
<p>It’s no wonder so many women believe that lash extensions are the best beauty tip they’ve ever received. Still, we have one more tip for you that might be just as good: rely on Ebenezer Eyelash for all your lash extension application and refill needs. We provide the <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/">best eyelash extensions in New York City</a>, provided by highly-trained and state-licensed lash artists committed to giving you the perfect lashes you deserve. Contact us today to learn more and to schedule your first – or next – lash extension application.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/22/the-best-beauty-tip-youll-ever-receive-get-lash-extensions/">The Best Beauty Tip You’ll Ever Receive: Get Lash Extensions!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/22/the-best-beauty-tip-youll-ever-receive-get-lash-extensions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Four Quick Questions to Help You Decide: Are Lash Extensions Right for You?</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/15/four-quick-questions-to-help-you-decide-are-lash-extensions-right-for-you/</link>
					<comments>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/15/four-quick-questions-to-help-you-decide-are-lash-extensions-right-for-you/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ebenezer Eyelash]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 07:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eyelash Advice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7855</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There’s no denying it: eyelash extensions continue to be one of the hottest beauty trends in the developed world. Each day, women across America are discovering just how great their lives can be when they can look in the mirror and see perfect lashes staring back at them. Of course, extensions are still new enough...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/15/four-quick-questions-to-help-you-decide-are-lash-extensions-right-for-you/">Four Quick Questions to Help You Decide: Are Lash Extensions Right for You?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There’s no denying it: <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/eyelash-extension-services/">eyelash extensions</a> continue to be one of the hottest beauty trends in the developed world. Each day, women across America are discovering just how great their lives can be when they can look in the mirror and see perfect lashes staring back at them. Of course, extensions are still new enough that large numbers of American women have yet to give them a try. If you’re one of those women, chances are that you are still on the fence about whether they’re the right beauty option for your needs. These four questions may help you with that decision.</p>
<h2><em>Are you satisfied with your natural lashes?</em></h2>
<p>When you look at your eyelashes, what do you see? Are they shorter than you wish they were? Do they lack that perfect curl, thickness, and lush look that you truly crave? The reality is that very few people are born with ideal lashes. For far too many women, short, straight, and lifeless lashes are commonplace. If you’ve always wished that your lashes had more to offer, then it’s a safe bet that you should probably consider a trip to your local eyelash extension salon.</p>
<h2><em>Would you like to set aside the mascara and give the natural look a try?</em></h2>
<p>According to most estimates, the average woman spends more than a year of her life putting on or removing makeup, including mascara and other eye makeup. What could you do with an entire extra year of added time? In addition, think of the wear and tear you’re putting your lashes through with all of those mascara applications and removals. With lash extensions, you can stop trying to create the illusion of perfect lashes and finally enjoy the real thing.</p>
<h2><em>Have you ever wished you had a little more glamor in your life?</em></h2>
<p>If you’ve ever watched your favorite actress or model flutter her flawless lashes, you’ve no doubt wondered what it would be like to have lashes that perfect. After all, who doesn’t want a little bit of glamor in her life? With extensions, you can have that glamorous look and always be the center of attention.</p>
<h2><em>Do you have a special event coming up and want to ensure that you look your best?</em></h2>
<p>Even if you’re not intent on looking glamorous every day, there are always those special occasions that merit that extra spot of star appeal. So, if you have a wedding, company event, graduation, or other special occasion looming on the horizon, a fresh new set of eyelash extensions could be just the accessory you need to make a splash.</p>
<p>At Ebenezer Eyelash, our lash artists are committed to helping you answer life’s most pressing beauty questions, by providing the best lash extensions in New York City. If you’re ready to enjoy all the benefits that come with a perfect set of eyelashes, then give us a call today and schedule your first – or next – lash extension application appointment.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/15/four-quick-questions-to-help-you-decide-are-lash-extensions-right-for-you/">Four Quick Questions to Help You Decide: Are Lash Extensions Right for You?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/09/15/four-quick-questions-to-help-you-decide-are-lash-extensions-right-for-you/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Need a Confidence Boost? Lash Extensions Can Help!</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/08/21/need-a-confidence-boost-lash-extensions-can-help/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ebenezer Eyelash]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 09:37:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eyelash extensions benefits]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7383</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are few things in life more important than confidence. Without it, it’s difficult to find success in your career, your familial relationships, or your love life. Unfortunately, most of us go through periods in our lives when our confidence is at a low point – and some of us have struggled with confidence issues...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/08/21/need-a-confidence-boost-lash-extensions-can-help/">Need a Confidence Boost? Lash Extensions Can Help!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are few things in life more important than confidence. Without it, it’s difficult to find success in your career, your familial relationships, or your love life. Unfortunately, most of us go through periods in our lives when our confidence is at a low point – and some of us have struggled with confidence issues for many years. Often, confidence in personal appearance is central to our overall confidence. Fortunately, there are things that you can do to enhance your appearance and give yourself that confidence boost that you need. One of the easiest options is to choose lash extensions!</p>
<h2>The “Eyes” Have It</h2>
<p>Confidence can begin with your eyes. When you meet a man with a steely gaze, you will almost certainly interpret that as a sign of his deep-seated confidence – and you’ll be right to do so. For a woman, though, the eyes can be even more revealing. They truly are the window to the soul! They’re powerful, expressive, and demanding of attention. That’s why so many women spend so much money and time on eye makeup, false eyelashes, and other tools and tricks to frame those wonderful orbs.</p>
<p>Well, eyelash extensions are the ultimate tool for enhancing your beautiful eyes. They won’t change your eyes, of course, but they will accentuate them and draw attention to them in ways that ordinary makeup simply cannot match. Whether your lashes are short, straight, lightly-colored, or drab and boring, lash extensions can revitalize them and give you the confidence that comes from knowing that your eyes always look their spectacular best.</p>
<h2>Ready at a Moment’s Notice</h2>
<p>Makeup may make you feel more confident from time to time, but it can sometimes have the opposite effect as well. There are times when it’s a struggle to get your makeup “on-point” and that can leave you feeling self-conscious and unsure of yourself. Sometimes, just the time invested in putting on your makeup can leave you feeling drained and at loose ends. With eyelash extensions, your lashes are always ready when you are. That means more time, more energy, and greater confidence that you can face the world without lengthy preparation</p>
<h2>Always Look Your Best</h2>
<p>Ultimately, though, your renewed sense of confidence will come from your lash extensions’ primary benefit: the ability to always look your absolute best. Most of the women who get eyelash extensions understand that they’re an easy way to get that “instant glam” that celebrities pay thousands and thousands of dollars to enjoy. And what could be more confidence-inspiring than looking more glamorous than you’ve ever looked before?</p>
<p>At Ebenezer Eyelash, we want the entire world to see you as the beautiful and confident person you know yourself to be. Our highly-trained and licensed lash technicians are always here to ensure that you get the perfect lash application you need to enjoy the confidence that you deserve. Give us a call today to schedule your next appointment, and discover the confidence that comes from having the <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/eyelash-extension-services/">best lash extensions in New York City</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/08/21/need-a-confidence-boost-lash-extensions-can-help/">Need a Confidence Boost? Lash Extensions Can Help!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Lashes Are Straight; Can Extensions Still Work for Me?</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/06/18/my-lashes-are-straight-can-extensions-still-work-for-me/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ebenezer Eyelash]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 05:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Straight Lashes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7210</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’ve seen your friends getting new eyelash extensions and felt like your straight lashes prevent you from enjoying that beauty enhancement, you’re not alone. There’s a fairly widespread belief out there that people with straighter lashes can’t really make these lash extensions work for them. Many of those women remain convinced that the only...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/06/18/my-lashes-are-straight-can-extensions-still-work-for-me/">My Lashes Are Straight; Can Extensions Still Work for Me?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you’ve seen your friends getting new eyelash extensions and felt like your straight lashes prevent you from enjoying that beauty enhancement, you’re not alone. There’s a fairly widespread belief out there that people with straighter lashes can’t really make these lash extensions work for them. Many of those women remain convinced that the only options available to them are lash curlers, perms, and a whole lot of mascara. But is that true? Do straight lashes preclude you from ever being able to experience the lush and perfectly-curled aesthetics that extensions can provide?</p>
<h2>Not a chance!</h2>
<p>Lash extensions can be an ideal solution for your straight, boring lashes, and can give you that perfect curl you’ve always dreamed of having – without regular perm treatments or time spent with a curler in hand. You can enjoy the same type of wake-up-perfect lashes that you see on your friends and loved ones, and spare yourself that morning eyelash-preparation ritual that is a part of so many women’s lives.</p>
<p>Here’s the thing to remember: with the right lash extensions, the curl is provided for you. Each extension is glued – one by one – to your natural eyelashes. And since the extensions are pre-curled, they provide you with the shape your lashes need for that full, vibrant look you’ve always dreamed of having. That means that your short, straight lashes can be transformed into long, lush, perfectly-curled lashes in just one session at the lash salon!</p>
<p>Of course, there are a few things to be aware of if you want to ensure that you get the results you need. After all, we’ve all heard those horror stories about women whose extensions have come out looking like matted hair on a sick animal, right? Well, that’s a rare event and one that you can avoid by adhering to a few simple rules:</p>
<ul>
<li>Rely on an eyelash salon that hires only licensed and experienced technicians to perform their applications. That’s the best way to ensure that your application is being performed by a real pro.</li>
<li>Make sure that you discuss your objectives with your technician before the application begins. That can help you avoid misunderstandings that could leave you feeling unsatisfied.</li>
<li>Listen to the care instructions that you’re provided when the application is complete. As great as these eyelash extensions can be for enhancing your appearance, the whole exercise is a waste of time if you’re not going to care for them properly when you leave the salon.</li>
</ul>
<p>At Ebenezer Eyelash, our technicians are all fully licensed in the state of New York, and fully trained to provide you with the lash extensions that you need to maximize your beauty potential. We’ll work with your straight lashes to provide you with the natural-looking curl and fullness that you seek, using only the safest products and application techniques available in the industry today. If you want to finally experience the <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/eyelash-extension-services/">best eyelash extensions in New York City,</a> call us to schedule your appointment today!</p>
<br />
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/06/18/my-lashes-are-straight-can-extensions-still-work-for-me/">My Lashes Are Straight; Can Extensions Still Work for Me?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Eyes Have It: How Your Eyelash Extensions Can Accentuate Your Image</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/05/19/the-eyes-have-it-how-your-eyelash-extensions-can-accentuate-your-image/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 07:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[confidence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eyelash Extensions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=6934</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Like most people, you’ve probably noticed how important beautiful eyes are when it comes to how people are viewed by others. After all, Marlowe might have written of Helen of Troy that hers was “the face that launched a thousand ships” &#8211; but it’s a pretty good bet that the eyes on that face played...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/05/19/the-eyes-have-it-how-your-eyelash-extensions-can-accentuate-your-image/">The Eyes Have It: How Your Eyelash Extensions Can Accentuate Your Image</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Like most people, you’ve probably noticed how important beautiful eyes are when it comes to how people are viewed by others. After all, Marlowe might have written of Helen of Troy that hers was “the face that launched a thousand ships” &#8211; but it’s a pretty good bet that the eyes on that face played a pretty big role in capturing the heart of young Paris. Face it; your eyes are often the first thing that people see when they look at your face, and the last thing they remember when you’ve bid them farewell.</p>
<p>Because of the powerful role the eyes play in projecting a person’s image to the world, women rightly focus much of their beauty attention on enhancements to showcase those beautiful orbs. For most, that means eyeliner, mascara, eyeshadow, lash perms, and even colored contacts. In recent years, however, another option for eye beauty enhancement has re-emerged: eyelash extensions. When done properly, a full and lush set of gently curled eyelash extensions can help to create the lasting impression every woman desires.</p>
<h2>Who Says the Eyes Matter?</h2>
<p>That’s always a good question to ask, right? Other than poets and people who write clever greeting cards, what evidence is there that the eyes are really that important when it comes to how others perceive us? Well, science says so. In fact, of the top five human features that people rate when judging someone’s attractiveness, the eyes consistently rate at or near the top of the list. Moreover, <a href="http://pss.sagepub.com/content/early/2014/07/15/0956797614539706">research</a> even indicates that the eyes are a central focus for serious interpersonal interaction.</p>
<p>All of that sees practical application in our efforts to shape, brighten, and highlight our eyes with all of the many tools and techniques mankind has developed over the centuries. Eyelash extensions might be a relative newcomer when it comes to eye-enhancing technologies, but they are taking the world by storm and providing many women with a great alternative to countless hours of lash curling and tinting.</p>
<p>However, there is a key to getting the most out of any set of lashes – and it isn’t found in those cheap drug store extension sets that you apply on your own. As any woman who’s ever tried those self-applications understands, that path lies to madness, sticky fingers, and a mass of clumped confusion where your lashes should be. To truly get the best results for your eyes, you need the lash applications that only trained and licensed professionals can provide.</p>
<p>At Ebenezer Eyelash, our licensed aestheticians are committed to helping you get the perfect lashes you deserve. Our unique application technique ensures that your lash works session will always exceed your expectations, as you receive the <a href="http://www.ebenezereyelash.com/">best eyelash extensions in New York City.</a> Enjoy the confidence and newfound inner strength that comes from knowing that your eyelashes always look their very best! To find out more about the benefits of lash extensions and schedule your next appointment at one of our salons, contact us today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/05/19/the-eyes-have-it-how-your-eyelash-extensions-can-accentuate-your-image/">The Eyes Have It: How Your Eyelash Extensions Can Accentuate Your Image</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Could Your Eyelash Extensions Ruin Your Natural Eyelashes?</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/05/08/could-your-eyelash-extensions-ruin-your-natural-eyelashes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ebenezer Eyelash]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 11:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eyelash damage]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7199</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Around the world, untold millions of women find themselves wishing that their eyelashes were somehow longer, fuller, or curled in a more pleasing way. These concerns are nothing new, of course, and have prompted a variety of different cosmetic trends throughout human history. It seems women – and some men – have always been searching...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/05/08/could-your-eyelash-extensions-ruin-your-natural-eyelashes/">Could Your Eyelash Extensions Ruin Your Natural Eyelashes?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Around the world, untold millions of women find themselves wishing that their eyelashes were somehow longer, fuller, or curled in a more pleasing way. These concerns are nothing new, of course, and have prompted a variety of different cosmetic trends throughout human history. It seems women – and some men – have always been searching for the perfect lash look. In recent years, that quest has focused on treatments like eyelash extensions, which offer women an opportunity to enhance their natural lashes. For some women, however, concerns about possible damage to their natural eyelashes have prevented them from experimenting with these lash treatments. So, what’s the verdict? Can extensions ruin your natural eyelashes?</p>
<h2>A Mixed Assessment</h2>
<p>There are some inherent difficulties when it comes to answering that type of question, largely because experiences have been so different for so many people. For millions of women, the application of lash extensions has resulted in the perfect, gorgeous lashes that they were looking for – without any side effects, discomfort, or real damage to those natural lashes. Meanwhile, other women have reported lash weakness and loss, or other similar complications. How can both types of result be true?</p>
<p>One thing is obvious: if most eyelash treatments cause no problems for the women who receive them, then it is clear that there is no inherent danger to the natural lash. That doesn’t explain the exceptions to that rule, however. Most experts believe that lash problems are in almost every instance the result of the type of application used to apply them. In other words, if you know someone whose natural lashes were damaged in any way by extensions, then the problem lies with the salon that did the application.</p>
<h2>What the Best Salons Do Differently</h2>
<p>It is important to recognize that poor lash extension jobs do not always indicate that the technician did a poor job. Sometimes, the problem is as simple as the type of adhesive used to affix each extension to that natural lash. Other times, the salon’s application technique is the problem. Even good technicians can have bad results when they’re working with inferior adhesives or are hamstrung by ineffective application techniques.</p>
<p>A truly professional salon avoids those problems by using only the best and safest adhesives in an application process designed to achieve the highest possible level of quality. Adhesives are applied with the utmost care to ensure that each extension is glued to only one lash, while avoiding direct contact with the skin. When done properly, there should never be any unexpected lash damage, including unnatural lash loss.</p>
<p>At <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/">Ebenezer Eyelash</a>, we take pride in ensuring that every eyelash extension we perform strictly adheres to the high standards we’ve set for ourselves and our clientele. Our licensed and professionally-trained lash professionals use only the safest adhesives and techniques during all applications, to provide you with the perfect lashes you’ve always wanted – without any unexpected complications. To learn more about how we can help you experience the best eyelash extensions in New York City, contact us today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/05/08/could-your-eyelash-extensions-ruin-your-natural-eyelashes/">Could Your Eyelash Extensions Ruin Your Natural Eyelashes?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Your Lash Look is Guaranteed to Be Unique</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/04/12/why-your-lash-look-is-guaranteed-to-be-unique/</link>
					<comments>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/04/12/why-your-lash-look-is-guaranteed-to-be-unique/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ebenezer Eyelash]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 04:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lashes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7829</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’ve been thinking about getting lash extensions for any length of time, chances are you’ve had many questions run through your mind. Among those may be questions about exactly how lash extensions will transform your appearance. Will your new lashes make you look like everyone else? How noticeable will they be? And perhaps most...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/04/12/why-your-lash-look-is-guaranteed-to-be-unique/">Why Your Lash Look is Guaranteed to Be Unique</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you’ve been thinking about getting lash extensions for any length of time, chances are you’ve had many questions run through your mind. Among those may be questions about exactly how lash extensions will transform your appearance. Will your new lashes make you look like everyone else? How noticeable will they be? And perhaps most important of all: are they even the right solution for my perfect lash needs? We have the answers you need, and those answers all point to one undeniable truth: your lash look is guaranteed to be unique.</p>
<h2>Lash Extensions Can’t Make You Look Like “One of the Crowd”</h2>
<p>First, let’s make this clear upfront: your new extensions won’t leave you looking like everyone else you know. Even if you and a friend selected the exact same lash extensions and the same application technique, you would still each come out of that experience looking strikingly different. Why is that? It’s simple.</p>
<p>We all have different facial features and our own unique look. Different bone structures. Different eye shape. Different brows. Different natural lashes. And so on. And while extensions can enhance your natural lashes, and make your eyes look bigger and brighter, they really have no ability to change any of the central characteristics that make you who you are. They can’t change your facial structure, skin tone, eye shape, or any of those other attributes that distinguish you from everyone around you. So no – you won’t ever look like anyone else in the crowd.</p>
<p>That is, unless you have a twin out there. But that’s a separate matter entirely.</p>
<h2>But Will they Be Noticeable?</h2>
<p>Ultimately, it’s really up to you and your lash artist to decide how noticeable your extensions will be. Are you looking for something dramatically different? If so, tell your lash artist and watch it become reality. If not, discuss your preferences and opt for something a little more understated. As we noted, it really comes down to what you want and how well you communicate those desires to your technician.</p>
<h2>Are they Right for Me?</h2>
<p>That last question is one that no one can answer but you. The fact is that millions of women have adopted lash extensions as an essential component of their beauty enhancement ritual. Many of them swear by their perfect lashes and couldn’t imagine going back to their previous dull and uninspired natural lash look. In the end, though, this is about you. Do you want longer, thicker, more perfectly-curled lashes – without mascara tricks or other techniques? If so, then extensions may very well be your best option too.</p>
<p>When you do decide to rely on lash extensions, make sure that you only choose the <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2018/12/28/get-instant-lash-perfection-with-eyelash-extensions/">best lash extensions in New York City</a>. The lash experts at Ebenezer Eyelash have the extensions you need to finally enjoy those perfect lashes you deserve. Give us a call today and we’ll be happy to answer your questions and schedule your perfect lash appointment at your convenience</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/04/12/why-your-lash-look-is-guaranteed-to-be-unique/">Why Your Lash Look is Guaranteed to Be Unique</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/04/12/why-your-lash-look-is-guaranteed-to-be-unique/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Making the Transition: From Mascara to Lash Extensions</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/03/25/making-the-transition-from-mascara-to-lash-extensions/</link>
					<comments>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/03/25/making-the-transition-from-mascara-to-lash-extensions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Ebenezer Eyelash]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 00:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mascara]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7824</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For many women, the hardest part of transitioning to lash extensions is getting past the need for mascara. Some lash-wearers still faithfully apply mascara on a regular basis, unable to set aside that old habit. Often, that constant application and removal of eye makeup ends up preventing them from fully enjoying their natural-looking extensions. In...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/03/25/making-the-transition-from-mascara-to-lash-extensions/">Making the Transition: From Mascara to Lash Extensions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For many women, the hardest part of transitioning to lash extensions is getting past the need for mascara. Some lash-wearers still faithfully apply mascara on a regular basis, unable to set aside that old habit. Often, that constant application and removal of eye makeup ends up preventing them from fully enjoying their natural-looking extensions. In some instances, those extension-wearers even find that their new lashes don’t last as long as they should due to that continual reliance on mascara. The problem is that many of them simply don’t realize that they no longer need that makeup to give the illusion of perfect lashes; their extensions already provide the real thing!</p>
<p>Still, we understand how difficult it can be to fully transition from mascara to lash extensions. That’s why we’ve compiled some of the most important facts you need to know to help you commit to a mascara-free life. Once you’ve seen the real benefits your extensions provide, you’ll appreciate just how unnecessary that mascara really is.</p>
<h2>Handling those Extensions</h2>
<p>First, let’s clear something up: your new lash extensions are not designed to be continually handled. Sure, you need to gently clean them every day, to keep them free of debris and bacteria. However, you don’t want to touch them any more than necessary – and that includes applying mascara. Every woman understands just how much attention mascara demands during application. Often, women have to apply several layers of mascara to achieve their desired look. But whether it’s one layer or three, one simple truth remains constant: whatever you put on your lashes eventually needs to be removed.</p>
<p>Unfortunately, that mascara-removal process requires you to touch, dab at, and otherwise handle your lashes. For extension-wearers, all that activity just increases the odds that you’ll weaken the adhesive bond and damage the lash. To avoid that, think twice before you reach for that mascara.</p>
<h2>You Don’t Need Mascara Anyway</h2>
<p>The other reason to set aside that mascara and trust your new extensions is even simpler to understand; you don’t need mascara when you have lash extensions. Remember, a great set of eyelash extensions gives you that extra length, volume, and curl that you’ve always tried to achieve with mascara and other lash enhancement techniques. If the goal is perfect lashes, then extensions are the solution you’ve been looking for. What can mascara really add to perfection? That’s right: nothing.</p>
<p>The bottom line is clear: eyelash extensions are your key to getting the perfect lashes of your dreams. Mascara and other eye makeup are simply unnecessary, since those extensions give you all the very real benefits you try to mimic with makeup. And since mascara can actually pose a risk to those extensions due to excessive handling of the lashes and potential weakening of the adhesive bond, they should be avoided whenever possible. Trust your extensions to give you that perfect lash look you deserve. For more information about how the <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/01/28/eyelash-extensions-why-theyre-worth-every-penny-you-pay/">best lash extensions in New York City</a> can benefit you, contact Ebenezer Eyelash today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/03/25/making-the-transition-from-mascara-to-lash-extensions/">Making the Transition: From Mascara to Lash Extensions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/03/25/making-the-transition-from-mascara-to-lash-extensions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
