<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>admin &#8211; The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/author/admin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 01:19:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Eyes Have It: How Your Eyelash Extensions Can Accentuate Your Image</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/05/19/the-eyes-have-it-how-your-eyelash-extensions-can-accentuate-your-image/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 07:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[confidence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eyelash Extensions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=6934</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Like most people, you’ve probably noticed how important beautiful eyes are when it comes to how people are viewed by others. After all, Marlowe might have written of Helen of Troy that hers was “the face that launched a thousand ships” &#8211; but it’s a pretty good bet that the eyes on that face played...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/05/19/the-eyes-have-it-how-your-eyelash-extensions-can-accentuate-your-image/">The Eyes Have It: How Your Eyelash Extensions Can Accentuate Your Image</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Like most people, you’ve probably noticed how important beautiful eyes are when it comes to how people are viewed by others. After all, Marlowe might have written of Helen of Troy that hers was “the face that launched a thousand ships” &#8211; but it’s a pretty good bet that the eyes on that face played a pretty big role in capturing the heart of young Paris. Face it; your eyes are often the first thing that people see when they look at your face, and the last thing they remember when you’ve bid them farewell.</p>
<p>Because of the powerful role the eyes play in projecting a person’s image to the world, women rightly focus much of their beauty attention on enhancements to showcase those beautiful orbs. For most, that means eyeliner, mascara, eyeshadow, lash perms, and even colored contacts. In recent years, however, another option for eye beauty enhancement has re-emerged: eyelash extensions. When done properly, a full and lush set of gently curled eyelash extensions can help to create the lasting impression every woman desires.</p>
<h2>Who Says the Eyes Matter?</h2>
<p>That’s always a good question to ask, right? Other than poets and people who write clever greeting cards, what evidence is there that the eyes are really that important when it comes to how others perceive us? Well, science says so. In fact, of the top five human features that people rate when judging someone’s attractiveness, the eyes consistently rate at or near the top of the list. Moreover, <a href="http://pss.sagepub.com/content/early/2014/07/15/0956797614539706">research</a> even indicates that the eyes are a central focus for serious interpersonal interaction.</p>
<p>All of that sees practical application in our efforts to shape, brighten, and highlight our eyes with all of the many tools and techniques mankind has developed over the centuries. Eyelash extensions might be a relative newcomer when it comes to eye-enhancing technologies, but they are taking the world by storm and providing many women with a great alternative to countless hours of lash curling and tinting.</p>
<p>However, there is a key to getting the most out of any set of lashes – and it isn’t found in those cheap drug store extension sets that you apply on your own. As any woman who’s ever tried those self-applications understands, that path lies to madness, sticky fingers, and a mass of clumped confusion where your lashes should be. To truly get the best results for your eyes, you need the lash applications that only trained and licensed professionals can provide.</p>
<p>At Ebenezer Eyelash, our licensed aestheticians are committed to helping you get the perfect lashes you deserve. Our unique application technique ensures that your lash works session will always exceed your expectations, as you receive the <a href="http://www.ebenezereyelash.com/">best eyelash extensions in New York City.</a> Enjoy the confidence and newfound inner strength that comes from knowing that your eyelashes always look their very best! To find out more about the benefits of lash extensions and schedule your next appointment at one of our salons, contact us today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2019/05/19/the-eyes-have-it-how-your-eyelash-extensions-can-accentuate-your-image/">The Eyes Have It: How Your Eyelash Extensions Can Accentuate Your Image</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Are DIY Lash Extensions a Good Idea?</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2017/02/06/are-diy-lash-extensions-a-good-idea/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 01:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DIY]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[problems]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7306</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Like many women, you’ve no doubt taken note of the latest beauty trend to burst onto the American consciousness. Yes, we’re talking about eyelash extensions – those magnificently perfect lash enhancements that can transform your eyes in ways that you never thought possible. You’ve probably even wondered what you’d look like with a set of...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2017/02/06/are-diy-lash-extensions-a-good-idea/">Are DIY Lash Extensions a Good Idea?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Like many women, you’ve no doubt taken note of the latest beauty trend to burst onto the American consciousness. Yes, we’re talking about eyelash extensions – those magnificently perfect lash enhancements that can transform your eyes in ways that you never thought possible. You’ve probably even wondered what you’d look like with a set of extensions on your own lashes. Most women can’t help but try to imagine themselves with those perfect, long lashes. Still, you might also be one of those women who wonders whether they’re enough like those temporary “false lashes” that you can simply put them on at home. In other words, are DIY lash extensions really a good idea?</p>
<p>The answer can be a little complex, since it depends on so many different factors. On the one hand, you could buy the extensions and adhesive, grab a mirror, and go through the process of trying to glue on each extension, one-by-one, until you’ve filled your lashes with long, curled extensions. If you’re extremely fortunate, you might even manage to do that without matting your lashes together, ruining the extensions, or getting any foreign substances in your eyes.</p>
<h2>Common DIY Lash Extension Problems</h2>
<p>Let’s be realistic, though – unless you’re using one-night-only extensions, chances are that any do-it-yourself extension effort is going to create more problems than you’re ready to experience. Just consider these common problems:</p>
<ul>
<li>The adhesive used by professionals can create skin irritation around the eyes if used improperly. It’s actually not the safest idea to be playing around with these adhesives at home – or any adhesive like them, for that matter.</li>
<li>Your lashes can end up matted together, which can create discomfort and cause distress for the natural lashes.</li>
<li>You’ll be working with one eye closed, which can lead to all sorts of miscalculations.</li>
<li>You won’t have the benefit that comes from having a trained professional managing the application. Again, that’s not an optimal situation for any lash extension application.</li>
</ul>
<h2>The Right Approach</h2>
<p>Here’s something to ponder while you consider whether it’s worth your while to give the old DIY extension application a try: professional lash extensions don’t typically sit around their homes giving themselves lash extensions. They rely on their fellow technicians to handle the job. Why? Because they understand the level of skill and experience needed to perform a proper application, and know how unsafe it can be to try the DIY option.</p>
<p>The fact that even the experts rely on other experts should give you pause. While there is always the chance that your DIY lash extension application could meet with resounding success, the odds are probably against you. At Ebenezer Eyelash, our expert technicians understand the amount of attention and skill that is needed for a proper lash extension, and are committed to ensuring that your application is done perfectly every time. If you’re considering lash extensions and want to avoid the potential pitfalls of a DIY application, call us today to learn how you can benefit from the <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/eyelash-extension-services/">best eyelash extensions in New York City</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2017/02/06/are-diy-lash-extensions-a-good-idea/">Are DIY Lash Extensions a Good Idea?</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Your Choice of Lash Salon is So Important</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2017/01/30/why-your-choice-of-lash-salon-is-so-important/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 04:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Lash Salon]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7302</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Have you been reading and hearing about the wonders of eyelash extensions, and perhaps find yourself intrigued by the idea? Are you picturing how you’d look with a fuller and more vibrant set of lashes? Millions of women have gone through that same thought process, and many of them are turning those imaginings into reality...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2017/01/30/why-your-choice-of-lash-salon-is-so-important/">Why Your Choice of Lash Salon is So Important</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Have you been reading and hearing about the wonders of eyelash extensions, and perhaps find yourself intrigued by the idea? Are you picturing how you’d look with a fuller and more vibrant set of lashes? Millions of women have gone through that same thought process, and many of them are turning those imaginings into reality by visiting their local lash salons to get the extension applications they so desperately crave. Before you just randomly pick a salon, however, it’s important to know what you should be looking for in a salon. That’s the only way to ensure that you get the service and results you deserve.</p>
<h2>Why It Matters</h2>
<p>Your eyelashes are a focal point for your beauty regimen. Many women spend years in search of the perfect mascara to give their lashes that full, perfect look that properly showcases their eyes. And since your lashes are so important, it makes sense to have only the best technicians handling them, right? After all, you wouldn’t let just anyone give you a tattoo or perform surgery on you. And you certainly don’t trust random hairdressers to cut and style your hair. You should be just as discriminating in your choice of lash salon.</p>
<p>Here’s the thing to remember: eyelash extensions are relatively easy to apply – but they’re difficult to apply correctly. As a result, it’s a lot simpler to make a mistake during the application process than it is to get the job done properly without errors. In the wrong hands, you could end up with seriously bad results. For example:</p>
<ul>
<li>If your technicians are inexperienced and improperly trained, you could end up clumped lashes, adhesive on your skin, or other poor results. Always make sure that you’re relying on a salon that hires only the best lash technicians.</li>
<li>Salons that use inferior adhesives can provide less than satisfactory applications. Lashes can fall off, clump together, or create other problems. Make sure that your chosen salon is using quality, safe adhesive for its applications.</li>
<li>You also need to make sure that your salon is using the right application technique. Some could take shortcuts and apply cluster lashes that won’t provide you with the same effects that you’ll receive with a proper extension application. If a salon doesn’t use a technique that applies one extension to each natural lash, go somewhere else.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Ask Questions!</h2>
<p>We understand how reluctant many people can be to ask a lot of questions about the products and services they buy. Sometimes, it just seems easier to go with the flow and deal with any consequences later. Here at Ebenezer Eyelash, we always recommend against that approach! You owe it to yourself to ask questions that can help you to feel more confidence that you’ve chosen the right salon for your needs. At our salons, we provide the <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/about-ebenezer-eyelash/">best eyelash extensions in New York City</a>, with professional applications by only the best, fully-licensed technicians. Give us a call to schedule your appointment today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2017/01/30/why-your-choice-of-lash-salon-is-so-important/">Why Your Choice of Lash Salon is So Important</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Five Things to Consider Before Getting Eyelash Extensions</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2017/01/18/five-things-to-consider-before-getting-eyelash-extensions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2017 03:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eyelash Extensions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7253</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With eyelash extensions growing in popularity with each passing day, it would be a little surprising if you hadn’t at least thought about adding them to your beauty repertoire. Many women see the results on their friends, and can’t help but be intrigued by the prospect of enhancing their own natural beauty with perfect lashes....</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2017/01/18/five-things-to-consider-before-getting-eyelash-extensions/">Five Things to Consider Before Getting Eyelash Extensions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With eyelash extensions growing in popularity with each passing day, it would be a little surprising if you hadn’t at least thought about adding them to your beauty repertoire. Many women see the results on their friends, and can’t help but be intrigued by the prospect of enhancing their own natural beauty with perfect lashes. You may even have planned to rush out and have an extension application, only to later hesitate out of a desire to learn more about these beauty wonders. That’s a natural thing to do, of course, and you should be educated before you make any decision like this. In fact, there are five specific things that you should consider before you get eyelash extensions.</p>
<ol>
<li>They’re not a short-term commitment. Unlike temporary falsies, these extensions have a longer lifespan. Typically, they’ll last as long as your natural lashes, which means that you can expect them to endure for anywhere from six weeks to two months – the natural life cycle of the average eyelash. That means that you need to be prepared to have them with you for the long haul.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="2">
<li>You’ll need a day of relative relaxation after your extensions. Your application needs time to set, to ensure that the adhesive holds properly. That means that you’ll need a day without showering, swimming, or washing your face. You should also avoid saunas, excessive outdoor activity – especially in the heat, and crying. Your best option is to make sure that you have a day of rest scheduled for the day after your application.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="3">
<li>There is maintenance involved. Lash extensions are not something you just get and then ignore. You need to cleanse them daily, and avoid lying on them when you’re asleep. For best results, you should also consider fill-in sessions between full applications, since lashes don’t necessarily all fall out at once.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="4">
<li>Your extensions will probably change your makeup routine. Once you get lash extensions, mascara may not be the only makeup that you set aside. Many women discover that they no longer need eyeliner, and many others find that they can limit their application of other makeup products too. It’s amazing what a powerful set of lashes can do.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="5">
<li>You’ll never look at your natural lashes the same way again. One thing’s for sure: once you see yourself with extensions, your natural lashes will always seem shorter, less full, and less vibrant than your beauty enhancements. That’s how great your extensions will make your lashes look!</li>
</ol>
<p>It’s always important to understand what you’re getting into when you make a big change like eyelash extensions. At Ebenezer Eyelash Extension, our technicians can answer many of the most pressing concerns you may have, while offering sage advice about how you can get the most out of your new lash extensions. If you’d like to learn more about how the <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/">best eyelash extensions in New York City</a> can enhance your appearance, self-confidence, and overall happiness, contact us today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2017/01/18/five-things-to-consider-before-getting-eyelash-extensions/">Five Things to Consider Before Getting Eyelash Extensions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Greet the New Year with New Lashes</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2017/01/17/greet-the-new-year-with-new-lashes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 04:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eyelashes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[new year]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[resolution]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7249</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Like many Americans, you’re probably excited at the prospect of the New Year and already hopeful that it will bring many positive changes in your life. For many women, the arrival of 2017 brings with it dreams that encompass a broad range of goals. If one of those goals involve bolstering your beauty routine, then...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2017/01/17/greet-the-new-year-with-new-lashes/">Greet the New Year with New Lashes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Like many Americans, you’re probably excited at the prospect of the New Year and already hopeful that it will bring many positive changes in your life. For many women, the arrival of 2017 brings with it dreams that encompass a broad range of goals. If one of those goals involve bolstering your beauty routine, then eyelash extensions can be a great place to start. New lashes can be the perfect way to motivate you to achieve many of your other main objectives in the coming year!</p>
<h2>Enjoy Greater Confidence</h2>
<p>Bold lashes are the “in” thing, and we all feel more confident when we know that we look our best. Beauty begins with the eyes, which is why things like mascara play such a critical role in our daily beauty rituals. Well, there’s no better way to accentuate that beauty than with powerful and easy-to-manage lash extensions. Enjoy the enhanced confidence that perfect lashes can provide!</p>
<h2>Focus on the Natural</h2>
<p>Chances are that you wouldn’t mind reducing the impact that makeup can have on your skin, so why not start by setting aside that mascara? Many women discover that their lash extensions help them to scale back on mascara and other eye makeup, since their bold new lashes do such a great job showcasing their eyes. Yes, your extensions can be the gateway that leads you back to that more natural look that you enjoyed in your youth – and that can have a tremendous impact on the health of your skin.</p>
<h2>Be More Punctual</h2>
<p>Okay, let’s be honest; getting eyelash extensions isn’t really going to make you be on time for work, social engagements, or family gatherings. But they can help you reduce the time spent on your makeup ritual, and that should theoretically give you more time to get to your destination before you’re late. If you’re anything like the rest of us, though, you’ll probably use that time to catch a few more minutes of sleep. Go ahead; we promise not to judge!</p>
<h2>Be the Star of Your Own Story!</h2>
<p>So many people talk about being the stars of their own lives, but how many people truly follow through on those statements? The fact is that you deserve to look and feel your best at all times, and eyelash extensions are an ideal way to make that happen. With new extensions, you’ll be more confident making eye contact with others, always ready to spring into action at the drop of a hat, and prepared to meet the challenges of the day. You’ll not only look and feel like a star; you’ll be a star too!</p>
<p>At Ebenezer Eyelash, we’re excited at the thought of all that 2017 might mean for you and all our clients. No matter what resolutions you’ve made for this coming year, keeping them will be easier when you have the best eyelash extensions in New York City powering your beauty routine. To find out how new lash extensions can help you greet the new year, contact us today.</p>
<br />
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2017/01/17/greet-the-new-year-with-new-lashes/">Greet the New Year with New Lashes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Perfect Lashes for Your Holiday Festivities</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/12/29/perfect-lashes-for-your-holiday-festivities/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 01:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[christmas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[holidays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[new year]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[party]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7206</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With winter almost here and the holiday atmosphere rapidly enveloping the country, many of us find our thoughts turning to those annual parties and other festivities. If you’re like most women, you want to ensure that you look your best for any special occasion, but the holiday season creates even more pressure to always show...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/12/29/perfect-lashes-for-your-holiday-festivities/">Perfect Lashes for Your Holiday Festivities</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With winter almost here and the holiday atmosphere rapidly enveloping the country, many of us find our thoughts turning to those annual parties and other festivities. If you’re like most women, you want to ensure that you look your best for any special occasion, but the holiday season creates even more pressure to always show up with the most dazzling look you can muster. To accomplish that feat, you need a strategy to really make sure that you shine – and new eyelash extensions can be a critical part of your plan!</p>
<h2>It’s All About the Eyes</h2>
<p>You’ve known it your entire life: your eyes are the centerpiece of your appearance! There’s a reason we obsess over our eyes, lashes, and eyebrows; women almost instinctively recognize that all beauty begins at the eyes. Your eyes draw in others during any personal encounter. They draw attention to you in any photograph. They linger in the minds of people that you meet – long after you’ve went your separate ways.</p>
<p>That’s why it’s so important to make sure that your eyes are on point in every respect. You want them big, bright, and beautiful. You need them to be properly showcased with just the right hair style, accented by perfectly-managed brows, and framed by the most beautiful eyelashes. For some women, that latter element is accomplished with mascara and a curler. For you, it can be best achieved with perfectly curled eyelash extensions.</p>
<h2>Extensions for Your Perfect Holiday Lashes</h2>
<p>With all of the parties and events the holidays have to offer, who wants to spend hours of time applying, removing, and reapplying mascara? With eyelash extensions, you can enjoy the following benefits:</p>
<ul>
<li>Perfect, long lashes that will enhance the brightness of your eyes, make you look even more alert and engaged, and help you look younger than you ever thought possible. Your friends and co-workers will be amazed!</li>
<li>Finally, you can put an end to mascara application and removal. Your extensions will be as full and dark as many mascara applications, ensuring that you have the ideal lashes for any social gathering.</li>
<li>You’ll receive the star treatment that you deserve. Your new lashes will dazzle everyone you see, providing a renewed sense of confidence and enabling you to put your own unique stamp on this year’s holiday season. Of course, it doesn’t hurt that you’ll look great in all those holiday photos too!</li>
</ul>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-7207" src="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/holiday-festivities-new-york-midtown.jpg" alt="Extensions for Your Perfect Holiday Lashes" width="710" height="399" srcset="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/holiday-festivities-new-york-midtown.jpg 710w, https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/holiday-festivities-new-york-midtown-300x169.jpg 300w, https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/holiday-festivities-new-york-midtown-100x56.jpg 100w" sizes="(max-width: 710px) 100vw, 710px" /></p>
<p>Eyelash extensions are simply the best present that you can give yourself this holiday season, and a sure way to make this time of year something to treasure for years to come. They’re safe, reasonably priced, and a perfect solution to all your holiday eye makeup challenges.</p>
<p>At Ebenezer Eyelash, we understand how important it is to put your best foot forward this time of year. Company parties, family gatherings, and other events can sometimes come in rapid succession. You can be ready for whatever comes your way by securing the best <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/eyelash-extension-services/">eyelash extensions in New York City</a>. Call us for your consultation and appointment today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/12/29/perfect-lashes-for-your-holiday-festivities/">Perfect Lashes for Your Holiday Festivities</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adapting to Eyelash Extensions</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/12/20/adapting-to-eyelash-extensions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 04:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adapting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eyelash Extensions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7202</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re ready to take the plunge and dive into the deep end of the eyelash extension pool, then it’s important to understand what you’re getting yourself into. Chances are that you’ve heard a great deal about the many benefits that great looking extensions can provide. The fact is, however, that you won’t be able...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/12/20/adapting-to-eyelash-extensions/">Adapting to Eyelash Extensions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you’re ready to take the plunge and dive into the deep end of the eyelash extension pool, then it’s important to understand what you’re getting yourself into. Chances are that you’ve heard a great deal about the many benefits that great looking extensions can provide. The fact is, however, that you won’t be able to enjoy those benefits to their fullest unless you learn to adapt your lifestyle to your new lash extensions. To do that, there are a few things that you definitely need to do:</p>
<h2>Understand the Process</h2>
<p>If you’re making eyelash extensions a part of your lifestyle, recognize that there’s a time commitment involved. Lash extensions need to be individually applied by professionals, and that takes times. That means that you need to commit to spending more than an hour in a salon every few weeks to maintain your perfect lashes over time.</p>
<h2>Your Makeup Needs Will Change</h2>
<p>Adapting to lash extensions often requires adaptations in your makeup routine. If you’re like many women, you’ll discover that you can often look your best with a more minimalist approach to makeup when you’re wearing eyelash extensions. Mascara is all but unnecessary, since your extensions will already be full, perfectly curled, and perfectly colored.</p>
<h2>Avoid Picking at Eyelashes</h2>
<p>Some people have a habit of pulling on their lashes or otherwise picking at them throughout the day. You’ll want to break that habit when you get extensions – unless you want to ruin the application and end up going in for a touch-up ahead of schedule. Extensions aren’t as frail as some might believe, but that doesn’t mean that they should be pulled, twisted, bent, or otherwise abused. Break those habits right now if you want your new lashes to have a chance to last.</p>
<h2>Cleansing Might Be Different</h2>
<p>Some people will recommend that you never get your lashes wet, and claim that it will weaken the extensions. While it’s true that you shouldn’t get them wet for the first day after your application, there’s no reason not to do so once that initial period is passed. In fact, you should cleanse them daily, splashing water in your eyes and applying a mild cleaning agent to the lashes to remove debris and bacteria. The main difference from your old cleaning ritual will be in the amount of interaction you have with the lashes. If you’re used to rubbing your eyes while cleaning them, skip that habit and adopt a gentle approach to cleaning.</p>
<p>The important thing to note here is that most of the changes you need to make are simple to adopt. Be prepared for the commitment in time, avoid doing things that could damage the lash extensions, and recommit to your cleansing routine. At Ebenezer Eyelash, our technicians can talk you through most of the changes that you’ll need to make and ensure that you have the knowledge you need to make your extensions last as long as possible. Contact us now to schedule your appointment to get the <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/eyelash-extension-services/">best eyelash extensions in New York City</a>.</p>
<br />
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/12/20/adapting-to-eyelash-extensions/">Adapting to Eyelash Extensions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Top Seven Reasons to Try Lash Extensions</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/12/06/the-top-seven-reasons-to-try-lash-extensions/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 03:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eyelash Extensions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7193</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eyelash extensions are one of the hottest beauty crazes to hit the scene in decades. Everywhere across the country, women are lining up to try out these wondrous eyelash makeovers, and finally enjoying the long, luscious, perfectly-curled lashes they’ve always dreamed of having. Like any other trend, though, it sometimes takes a while to convince...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/12/06/the-top-seven-reasons-to-try-lash-extensions/">The Top Seven Reasons to Try Lash Extensions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eyelash extensions are one of the hottest beauty crazes to hit the scene in decades. Everywhere across the country, women are lining up to try out these wondrous eyelash makeovers, and finally enjoying the long, luscious, perfectly-curled lashes they’ve always dreamed of having. Like any other trend, though, it sometimes takes a while to convince some people to give them a try. If you’ve yet to experience the joys of eyelash extensions, here are the top seven reasons you should try them today.</p>
<ol>
<li>The application is quick, it’s painless, and it works! Your extensions will generally take about an hour or less to apply, and the experience is so relaxing that we may have to wake you up when the process is complete.</li>
<li>Lashes are safe to apply, and easy to wear. Each lash is individually glued to your natural eyelashes, one by one. The adhesive that we use is safe and durable, and our process is designed to ensure that you don’t end up with clumped lashes or other unsightly botches.</li>
<li>You can cut down on your makeup. Many women find that their lash extensions are so dramatic that they’re able to reduce the amount of makeup that they use elsewhere on their face. You’ll be amazed to see the impact that a perfect set of eyelashes can have on your overall appearance!</li>
<li>You can start skipping the mascara. If you’re one of those women who spends an inordinate amount of time every morning fretting over your mascara, these extensions can remedy that situation. Since extensions eliminate the need for mascara, you can even set your alarm a little later in the morning and catch a few extra minutes of well-deserved sleep.</li>
<li>If you’ve ever had lash curling or tinting done, then you already know how great your lashes can look when they’re detailed for perfection. Well, your eyelash extensions will help you to avoid those treatments, as they’re designed to give you just the curl and color you need to enhance your personal beauty.</li>
<li>Your new lash extensions will have you feeling and looking fresh throughout each day. No more of that droopy-eyed sleepy appearance that we’ve all experienced. Your eyes will look vibrant and alive, from morning to night.</li>
<li>You deserve to pamper yourself. Look, you work hard and you play hard. And chances are that your life is so busy that there’s always a lot more of the former than the latter! Isn’t it about time you did something just for you?</li>
</ol>
<p>At Ebenezer Eyelashes, our experienced lash technicians are committed to ensuring that each client walks out of the salon with a perfect lash extension application that enhances their beauty. Our extensions are the safest and most attractive applications available anywhere in the area, and our unique application process ensures that your eyelashes will always look their best. To find out how the <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/eyelash-extension-services/">best eyelash extensions in New York City</a> can maximize your appearance, contact us today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/12/06/the-top-seven-reasons-to-try-lash-extensions/">The Top Seven Reasons to Try Lash Extensions</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Losing Lashes Unexpectedly: Extensions Can Help!</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/11/27/losing-lashes-unexpectedly-extensions-can-help/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 23:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eyelash loss]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7178</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you’re like most women, you’ve had a time or twelve when you’ve found yourself worrying about an increase in the rate at which your eyelashes fall out. Chances are that your worries passed fairly quickly as the situation returned to normal within a few short days. That’s a common phenomenon, since lashes have a...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/11/27/losing-lashes-unexpectedly-extensions-can-help/">Losing Lashes Unexpectedly: Extensions Can Help!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you’re like most women, you’ve had a time or twelve when you’ve found yourself worrying about an increase in the rate at which your eyelashes fall out. Chances are that your worries passed fairly quickly as the situation returned to normal within a few short days. That’s a common phenomenon, since lashes have a natural cycle of growth and shedding that usually sees perhaps two eyelashes fall out every day – sometimes more and sometimes less. The real worry occurs when lashes start falling out in groups! If that happens, you may have some bad habits that are causing the excessive shedding. The good news is that eyelash extensions may be the solution you need.</p>
<h2>Are You Rubbing Too Much?</h2>
<p>If you’re rubbing your eyelashes during your makeup removal process, you could be creating stress to the lashes. This can lead to lashes falling out due to the trauma your makeup routine creates. It’s a risk that most women face when they rely on mascara to beautify their lashes.</p>
<h2>Are You Curling Your Lashes?</h2>
<p>If you’re committed to regular curling of your lashes, you should know that your use of the curler could be putting undue stress on those delicate natural lashes. You could even be pulling them out without knowing it, especially when you’re using your curler on lashes that already have mascara on them. Sometimes, lashes just aren’t up to the task of enduring all that stress.</p>
<h2>Do You Forget to Remove Your Mascara?</h2>
<p>Almost every woman eventually goes to sleep with mascara on. If so, then chances are that you’ve had lashes break or fall off while you’re sleeping. Why? It’s simple. Mascara causes the lash to harden somewhat, and that makes them more brittle. When they make contact with your pillow, those hardened lashes can sometimes break.</p>
<h2>How Lash Extensions Can Help</h2>
<p>If you’re suffering ongoing lash loss due to these common habits, eyelash extensions might be the solution you need. Here’s why:</p>
<ul>
<li>With extensions, you no longer need mascara. That means that you won’t need to rub your eyes to remove the makeup. Instead, you only need gentle daily lash cleansings to remove bacteria and debris.</li>
<li>Your extensions have a natural curl. When attached to your natural lashes, you get the perfectly-curled lashes you need without subjecting yourself to the rigors of the lash curler.</li>
<li>You’ll also never have to worry about forgetting to remove that mascara, since you won’t be wearing it. Your new lashes will already have that full, perfectly-tinted look you need, and won’t be so brittle that they break off when you’re asleep.</li>
</ul>
<p>Obviously, eyelash extensions aren’t some miracle product that can resolve all your lash problems, but they could be the solution to some of the most common lash loss difficulties you might be facing. If you’re experiencing persistent unexplained lash loss and want to know whether you could benefit from the <a href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/">best eyelash extensions in New York City</a>, contact us today to schedule your next extension application appointment.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/11/27/losing-lashes-unexpectedly-extensions-can-help/">Losing Lashes Unexpectedly: Extensions Can Help!</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eyelash Extensions and the Perfect Bride</title>
		<link>https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/11/19/eyelash-extensions-and-the-perfect-bride/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2016 17:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bride]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[eyelashes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[wedding]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/?p=7169</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What does it take to achieve that “perfect bride” look you dreamed about as a child? That’s a question that many women ponder as the big day approaches, and everyone seems to approach it in a different way. Many have their own visual image of what an ideal bride should look like, often drawn from...</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/11/19/eyelash-extensions-and-the-perfect-bride/">Eyelash Extensions and the Perfect Bride</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What does it take to achieve that “perfect bride” look you dreamed about as a child? That’s a question that many women ponder as the big day approaches, and everyone seems to approach it in a different way. Many have their own visual image of what an ideal bride should look like, often drawn from long-held childhood imaginings and romanticized visions of perfection. Others search bridal magazines and huddle with experts in an attempt to determine just how they should present themselves to the world on their wedding day.</p>
<p>In reality, presenting yourself as the perfect bride at your own wedding shouldn’t be such an angst-ridden decision. It’s you that everyone is coming to see, so your only concern should be to present the best possible version of yourself that you can. And no, that doesn’t mean getting a complete makeover or trying to make yourself look like someone else. It means enhancing those gorgeous features that you already possess. And when it comes to enhancing features, eyelash extensions can be any perfect bride’s best friend.</p>
<h2>Meeting Your Wedding Goals</h2>
<p>Just think about all of the things you want to accomplish with your look while you’re tying the knot on your wedding day. You want all eyes on you. You want to dazzle your groom and every guest at the venue. You want to bring to life your own perfect wedding day in a way that everyone will remember for decades to come. And, of course, you want to look your best in those millions of photos that are sure to be taken throughout the course of the day.</p>
<p>Eyelash extensions can accomplish all of those goals. With extensions, your eyes will be perfectly enhanced with long, perfectly-curled lashes that provide the perfect blend of flirty fun and engaging elegance. You’ll look great from every angle, give the camera a once-in-a-lifetime thrill, and have the freedom to even shed a tear of joy if the mood strikes you &#8211; and you won’t have to worry about your mascara running, because there won’t be any!</p>
<h2>Doing it Right</h2>
<p>There are some things you should consider before you get your extensions, of course:</p>
<ul>
<li>Start wearing eyelash extensions several months before your wedding, just so you have a chance to get used to the look and feel.</li>
<li>Be sure to get your wedding lashes done several days prior to the wedding so that they will look their absolute best. Besides, it’s such a relaxing experience that it might help to calm any pre-wedding jitters you might be experiencing.</li>
<li>Get your extensions applied by certified and licensed experts to ensure quality and safety.</li>
</ul>
<p>And when it comes to experts, rely on the professionally trained and New York-licensed technicians at Ebenezer Eyelash. Our staff will ensure that you receive the individually-applied lash extensions you need to help you achieve your perfect bride look. If you want the best eyelash extensions in New York City for your wedding day beauty enhancements, contact us today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com/2016/11/19/eyelash-extensions-and-the-perfect-bride/">Eyelash Extensions and the Perfect Bride</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ebenezereyelash.com">The Best Eyelash Extensions in NYC – Ebenezer Eyelash Extension</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
